Hi, my name is Regen Tolentino.
You can call me John.
I'm 24 years old.
I have a 3-year work experience with the BPO industry, doing inbound and outbound
calling.
First, I served as a technical consultant wherein my multitasking skills has been
definitely enhanced.
Then eventually I switched to customer service where in our integrity plays a very
big role.
Definitely sales must always be on point ahead of the target, and at the same time
making sure that each and every customer will always be satisfied with my assistance
.
And on top of all these skills, I also have a talent with doing graphic designs, creating
flyers, business cards, and social media advertisements, which will really be helpful
for clients' marketing needs.
And I can assure you that I'm not just gonna be another number on your payroll, but
definitely a good addition to your company.
Once again, this is Re John Tolentino.
Thank you and goodbye.